## Felipe Teixeira de Oliveira

74 Leeson Street Lower, Dublin 2, Ireland, 0834392586, felipetoliveira@outlook.com.br

#### **PROFILE**

Recently graduated with a Higher Diploma in Computer Science from CCT College in Dublin/Ireland. My skills include technologies such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java and MySQL. Currently, I am working by myself on enhancing my JavaScript skills and have created a portfolio to showcase all the learning projects I am developing with URL <u>felipeteixeira.dev</u>. My academic training is complemented by a solid practical experience of more than 6 years in Civil Engineering working in an estimating department with Excellent Microsoft Office knowledge.

#### **EDUCATION**

Sep 2022 — Oct 2023

Higher Diploma Science in Computing (NFQ level 8), CCT College

Dublin (Ireland)

#### Graduated with 2st Class Honours.

**Modules included:** Databases; Networking & Virtualization; Software development; Web development; Cloud based web applications; Algorithms & constructs; Mobile development.

#### Final Project: Developed an app for a garage company to organize their appointments.

- Developed a front-end app using HTML, CSS, and the Ionic Framework.
- · Enabled the company to register new employees and print receipts.
- · Allowed users to create accounts, register their cars, and schedule appointments.

# Portfolio: I developed a website portfolio to include all my own projects that I'm working on by myself to improve my skills.

- The webpage still undergoing development and updates using HTML and CSS technologies.
- · At the moment, I'm studying JavaScript to make my page dynamic and interactive with users.
- You can find all my details there: felipeteixeira.dev.

Oct 2020 — Oct 2021

Postgraduate Business (NFQ level 8), Cruzeiro do Sul University São Paulo (Brazil)

Graduated with 1st Class Honours.

Jan 2012 — Aug 2018

Bachelor Degree Civil Engineering (NFQ level 8), Anhembi Morumbi University São Paulo (Brazil)

Graduated with 2st Class Honours.

#### RELEVANT EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Jan 2022 — Jan 2024

#### Site Manager, GS Associates.

Dublin (Ireland)

- · Creating staff schedules and managing weekly budgets.
- Organizing and archiving contracts.
- Meeting with general managers for their weekly feedback.
- · Keeping training records.
- Managing daily tasks and managers' requests.
- Using Word, Excel, and Outlook on a daily basis.

Jun 2021 — Oct 2021

## Quality Engineer / Quantity Surveyor, Modo Construction.

São Paulo (Brazil)

- Assisting the Senior QS to manage subcontract packages and overseeing payments to
- $\bullet \;\;$  subcontractors with works measurement and photographic reports.
- · Assisting the Senior QS to assist with the preparation of monthly internal valuations and monthly
- · cost reports.
- · Reporting on budgets and variations.
- · Daily and photography Reports.
- Daily use of Word, Excel, Outlook, AutoCAD.

## Junior Enginner, Consfat Engineering.

- São Paulo (Brazil)
- · Commercial rooms and shopping center renovations management.
- Quantity surveying with AutoCAD and Excel.
- Project review management.
- Architectural and AS-BUILT drawings in AutoCAD.
- · Works measurement and photographic report.
- · Daily fields report.
- Quotation of material/equipment update.
- Daily use of Word, Excel, Outlook, AutoCAD.

April 2015 — Sept 2018

## Quantity Surveyor/Estimator, Arbore Engineering.

São Paulo (Brazil)

- · Assisting the Senior QS in quantity surveying using AutoCAD and PDF drawings and Excel.
- Assisting the Senior QS to manage subcontract packages and overseeing payments to subcontractors with works measurement.
- Assisting the Senior QS to assist with the preparation of monthly internal valuations and monthly cost reports to analyze progress and budgets and variations.
- Control of drawing revisions for all subjects.
- Quotation of material/equipment update.
- Modelling architectural and structural projects in Revit 3D.
- Daily use of Word, Excel, Outlook, AutoCAD e Revit.

Jun 2014 — Nov 2014

## Quantity Surveyor/Estimator, Pillaster Constructor.

São Paulo (Brazil)

- · Assisting the Senior QS in quantity surveying using AutoCAD drawings and Excel.
- Assisting the Senior QS in the preparation of the cost spreadsheet including updated quotation and material quantity surveying.
- Maintenance of drawings registers and control of drawing revisions.
- Quotation of material/equipment update.
- · Daily use of Word, Excel, Outlook.

Aug 2013 — May 2014

## Quantity Surveyor/Estimator, Tiberio Engineering.

São Paulo (Brazil)

- Assisting the Senior QS in quantity surveying using AutoCAD drawings and Excel.
- Assisting the Senior QS in the preparation of the cost spreadsheet including updated quotation and material quantity surveying.
- Maintenance of drawings registers and control of drawing revisions.
- Quotation of material/equipment update.
- Daily use of Word, Excel, Outlook.

LANGUAGES

English

Working Knowledge

Portuguese

Native speaker

REFERENCES

References available upon request